The amps are on but nobody's home.
Airheads is a comedy, crime, music film directed by Michael Lehmann.
The Lone Rangers have heavy-metal dreams and a single
demo tape they can't get anyone to play.
The solution: Hijack an FM rock radio station and hold the deejays
hostage until they agree to broadcast the band's tape.
Chester 'Chazz' Darvey, played by Brendan Fraser.
Rex, played by Steve Buscemi.
Pip, played by Adam Sandler.
Ian, played by Joe Mantegna.
Officer Wilson, played by Chris Farley.
Jimmie Wing, played by Judd Nelson.
Airheads is a 1994 American comedy film directed by
Michael Lehmann and written by Rich Wilkes.
It stars Brendan Fraser, Steve Buscemi, and Adam Sandler as the members of a struggling rock
band who hijack a Los Angeles radio station in order to get their demo aired.
The rest of the principal cast includes Chris Farley, Michael McKean, Judd Nelson, Michael Richards,
and Joe Mantegna, with Ernie Hudson, Amy Locane, Nina Siemaszko, Marshall Bell, Reg E.
Cathey, and David Arquette in supporting roles.
Airheads was a critical and commercial failure, but has
since come to be viewed as a cult film.
The film explores themes of radio station, heavy metal, rock band.
The tone is lighthearted.